{
    "id": "682ccdae7c9643a192d3f1aae21f1b2b",
    "title": "Gap Filling Exercise (Intermediate Level)",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "40ec602a0d4b49578299e440d65aeaa4",
            "title": "Gap Filling Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "At least six people have ……………….. in the explosion.",
                    "description": "Died is the past tense of die.",
                    "answers": [
                        "dies",
                        "died",
                        "dead"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "By the time they found him, he was already ……………………….",
                    "description": "Dead is an adjective. Died is a verb. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "died",
                        "dead"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She …………………… in the morning.",
                    "description": "The simple past is used when we say when something happened.",
                    "answers": [
                        "left",
                        "has left",
                        "leaved"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Let’s ………………………. your plans.",
                    "description": "Discuss is one of those verbs that are not followed by a preposition.",
                    "answers": [
                        "discuss",
                        "discuss about",
                        "discuss over"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………………… him a visit the other day.",
                    "description": "Paid is the past tense of pay.",
                    "answers": [
                        "payed",
                        "paid",
                        "have paid"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You haven’t …………………….. for your drinks.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "payed",
                        "paid",
                        "pay"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She …………………….. her dress and went out.",
                    "description": "To put on dress is to wear it. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "took on",
                        "put on",
                        "brought on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "What a brilliant idea ……………………..!",
                    "description": "The inverted word order is used in exclamations.",
                    "answers": [
                        "is it",
                        "it is",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Tell me why ………………………. to leave now.",
                    "description": "The inverted word order is used in indirect questions. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "want you",
                        "do you want",
                        "you want"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "You ……………………… listen to your doctor.",
                    "description": "Had better is used to give strong advice or warnings.",
                    "answers": [
                        "have better",
                        "had better",
                        "had to better"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you started early, you …………………….. miss the bus.",
                    "description": "In the second conditional, we use a simple past tense in the if-clause and would + first form of the verb in the main clause.",
                    "answers": [
                        "won't",
                        "wouldn't",
                        "hadn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "A cousin of ………………….. is an actor.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "me",
                        "my",
                        "mine"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}